제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
토요일 오후
Saturday Afternoon
오후 3시 42분
3:42 p.m.
에릭네 지하실
Eric Forman's Basement
- 니들 여태 그걸 안 했단 말야?
- 그러니까 이번에 했다구!
- You and Jackie did not do it.
- No. We so did it.
너 맨날 한 것 처럼 말했었잖아
You're always saying
that you did it.
켈소, 넌 여태 재키 바지도
못 벗겨 본 거야
Kelso, she wears the pants,
and they have never come off.
내 얼굴을 봐
이 딱지뗀 어르신의 얼굴을 보라구
Look at my face.
This is a face that did it.
젠장, 진짜 했나 봐
Holy smokes, I think he did it.
- 켈소가 했다!
- 나 했다!
- Kelso did it!
- I did it!
축하한다, 친구
Yeah. Congratulations, man.
- 아주 일찌감치도 해치웠구나
- 그렇게 생각해?
- Plus, you did it in record time.
- Yeah, you think?
아니, 이 바보야. 너 일년이 넘도록
걔 엉덩이만 쫓아다녔잖아
No, you moron. You've been
kissing her ass for over a year.
맞아, 그치만 그것도 이제 끝이야
Yeah, but that's over, man.
아직도 총각인 너희 어린 것들에게
설명하기는 어렵지만
It's hard to explain to you kids
that have never had sex before...
그걸 하게 되면 여자한테 뭔가
화학적 변화가 생긴다고
but when you're with a woman,
something chemical happens to her.
재키는 이제 완전히 변했어
내 사랑의 노예가 됐다니까
Now, Jackie is totally different.
She's like my love slave.
내가 그만큼 잘한다는 거지
Yeah, I'm that good.
안녕, 얘들아
Hey, guys.
안녕, 자기
오늘 기분은 어때?
Hi, sweetie. How are you?
사실 약간 으스스한데
코트를 차에다 두고 왔어
Actually, I'm a little bit chilly.
But I left my coat up in the car.
내가 갖다 줄게
이따 봐요
I'll go get it for you.
Miss me.
아주 편리하지 않냐?
Handy little thing, isn't she?
이야, 정말 죽이는데
Okay, that was so cool.
죽여? / "죽인다"는 게
"바보같고 나쁜 짓"이란 뜻이야
Cool? / And by "cool" I mean
"wrong and stupid."
야, 조용히 해봐
레슬링 다시 시작한다
All right, shut up.
Wrestling's back on.
난 레슬링이 좋아!
I love wrestling!
야, 왜 반격하지 않는 거야?
Come on, you're not
even fighting back.
그 좋은 데서 왜 풀려나고 싶겠냐?
Why would he fight back?
잊지 마십시요
이번 토요일 저녁
Don't forget,
this Saturday night...
위스콘신주 케노샤시 체육관에서
프로 레슬링 시합이 열립니다
pro wrestling is coming...
to the National Guard Armory
in Kenosha, Wisconsin.
로키 존슨이 난폭한 난쟁이
20명을 상대합니다
Watch Rocky Johnson
take on 20 snarling midgets.
이제, 경기 다시 보시죠
Now, back to the action.
로키 존슨이 케노샤에 온다고?
야, 우리 가자
Rocky Johnson's coming to
Kenosha? Man, we gotta go.
나도 갈래
난 난쟁이들이 좋아
I'm in. I love midgets, man.
- 에릭, 좀 올라와 봐라
- 네, 금방 갈게요
- Eric, I need to see you up here.
- Okay, I'll be right up.
너 안 올라가 봐?
You are not going up?
이거 보고 올라갈 거야
I'll go up when I'm ready.
그래서 제 자신에게 말했죠
So I just said to myself:
"돈 한푼 없이 가진 거라곤
더러운 빨래 밖에 없어도 상관없어"
"I don't care if all I have
is dirty laundry and no money.
"난 부모님이 계신 집으로 갈거야
난 그분들을 너무 사랑하니까"
"I'm going home to see my parents.
Because I love them very much."
어쩜
Oh, my.
저기, 이거 좀 볼래요?
Well, will you look at these?
엄마, 요새 여자애들은
다 그런 거 입어요
Yeah, Mom, all the girls
are wearing them.
에릭, 왜 인제 와?
Eric, where have you been?
그래, 내가 5분 전에 불렀잖아
Yeah, Eric, I called you
five minutes ago.
레슬링 보고 있었어요
I was watching wrestling.
내가 시킨 대로
도서관에 책 반납했냐?
Did you take those books
back to the library like I asked you?
네, 반납했어요
Yeah. I took them back.
그런데 왜 그 책들이
네 차 뒷좌석에 있는 거냐?
Then why did I see them
in the backseat of your car?
일단 차에다 반납했거든요
I took them back to the car.
사실상 도서관에
반납된 거나 다름없죠
Which means that
they're practically at the library.
있죠 아빠, 그 책들을 읽고 싶어할
착한 아이들이 너무 안됐어요
You know, Dad,
I feel sorry for all the good kids...
who wanted to read those books.
얼마나 책을 읽고 싶을까
That's who I feel sorry for.
알았어요, 5권인데 권당 연체료가
5센트니까 제가 25센트 낼게요
Okay, it's five books. A nickel a book.
Big deal, I'm out a quarter.
돈이 문제가 아니다
법규를 지켜야지
It's not about the money, son.
It's about the rules.
법규를 안 지키면
우리 모두 나무에 기어올라 가서
And without rules,
we might as well all be up in a tree...
헛소리나 날리고 있게 될거야
flinging our crap at each other.
알았어요
Okay.
도서관은 30분 뒤에 문을 닫으니까
잽사게 튀어가
The library closes in a half an hour,
so get your ass over there.
아빠, 제 친구들이 전부 저 밑에서...
Dad, you know,
all my friends are downstairs so--
얘야, 날 나쁜 사람 만들지 마라
Hey, pal, I'm not
the bad guy here.
책을 반납하지 않아
무덤을 판건 너야
Now, you screwed yourself
when you didn't return those books.
어서 가
Now go.
알았어요
Okay.
싫어요
No.
너 지금 "싫다"고 했냐?
Did you say, "no"?
너 지금 나한테 "싫다"고 한 거야?
Are you telling me, "no"?
내가 제대로 들은 거냐?
Is that what I'm hearing?
네..
Yeah.
오, 이런
Oh, dear.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x15 That Wrestling Show
Feb 07, 1999 on FOX
재밌는게 뭔지 알아요?
You know what's interesting?
아니
No.
당신은 로리하고는
대화를 하면서
When you talk to Laurie,
you actually have a conversation...
에릭한테는
명령만 한다는 거예요
but with Eric, you just give orders.
그 녀석이 반항하잖아
Kitty, he said no to me.
걔도 이제 컸어요, 여보
He's getting older, Red.
내 생각엔 부자간에
우정을 쌓아야 할 것 같아요
I think it's time you two
developed a friendship...
안 그러면, 에릭이 집을 나가서
다시는 걜 못 볼지도 몰라요
'cause if you don't, he'll move away
and we'll never see him again.
그걸 원하는 건 아니죠?
Is that what you want?
여보!
Red.
에릭하고 무슨 놈의 우정이야?
I can't be friends with Eric.
그 녀석은 너무...
He's too twitchy.
방정맞잖아
당신이 뭔가 노력하는
모습을 보일 때까지
Red, until I see you
make some kind of effort...
계속 이걸로 잔소리할 거예요
I'm just gonna keep bringing it up.
협박은 안 통해
Threats aren't gonna work, Kitty.
당신이 신문 볼 때마다
In the middle of every newspaper
you're reading...
낮잠을 잘 때마다
축구 경기 볼 때마다
every nap you're taking,
every football game you're watching...
계속 잔소리 할 거예요
잔소리, 잔소리, 잔소리!
I'll be there talking. Talking, talking,
talking, talking.
여보, 나 심리치료를 시작할까 봐요
Bob, I'm thinking of starting therapy.
저는 이만..
Okay, I'm gonna be....
갈께요
Bye.
심리치료?
Therapy? That's for crazies.
미친 것들이나 하는 거잖아
자아를 확인하지 않고는
자아실현을 할 수 없어요
You know, the unexamined self
is an unfulfilled self.
당신이 자아실현을 왜 못해?
How can you be unfulfilled?
내가 집 사줬지, 세금 다 내 주지
당신을 먹여 살리고 있잖아
I put a roof over your head,
I pay the bills, I take care of you.
맞아요, 그치만 난 뭘하는 거죠?
- Yeah, but what do I do?
- You fill out that sweater real nice.
그 스웨터를 아주 멋지게
소화해내고 있잖아
당신 정말
You are so...
매정해요!
cold!
뭐가?
칭찬해 줘도 난리야
What? That's a compliment.
로리, 이리 와서 갈비 좀 먹으렴
Sit down, Laurie, have some ribs.
엄마, 내가 요구르트 다이어트
시작한 거 아시잖아요
Mom, you know
I'm on my water and yogurt diet.
정말 멋지죠?
Okay, isn't this nice?
가족이 다같이 둘러 앉았네요
My whole family together. Mostly.
거의 다요
가족끼리 즐거운 시간을 갖는 것
그게 저녁식사의 목적 아니겠어요?
Having family fun.
Because that's what dinner is for.
안 그래요, 여보?
Right, Red?
알았어
Okay.
그래, 에릭
So. Eric...
오늘 학교에서는 어떤 일이 있었냐?
what happened at school today?
왜요? 무슨 말을 들으셨는데요?
Why? What'd you hear?
대체 왜 그러는 거냐?
난 이런 평범한 질문도 하면 안 되냐?
What's wrong with you?
I can't ask a simple question?
여보, 감자 좀 드세요
Red, you need some potatoes.
책 반납하고 오느라 수고했다
Good job on returning those books.
네, 책은 반납했어요
Yeah, I returned the books.
바보같은 짓이었지만 말이죠
Even though it was kind of stupid.
뭐?
What?
바보같은 짓이랬어요, 아빠
He said it was stupid, Daddy.
좋아요, 좋아
Okay. Okay.
에릭, 이번 주말에 뭐 할 거니?
Eric, what are you gonna
do this weekend?
애들하고 케노샤에
레슬링 시합 보러 갈거예요
Me and the gang are gonna catch
that wrestling match in Kenosha.
어머 이런 우연이?
Now, isn't that something?
레드 포먼 씨도 고등학교 때
레슬링을 했었거든
Because a certain Mr. Red Forman
used to wrestle in high school.
아냐. 내가 했던 건 진짜였어
No. What I did then was real.
TV에 나오는 그딴 건..
다 쇼일 뿐이야
That stuff on TV, that's all an act.
글쎄요
I don't know.
둘이서 같이 가면
정말 재밌을 거예요
I bet if the two of you went together,
you'd really enjoy yourselves.
그렇죠?
Right, guys?
- 싫어요 엄마, 전..
- 내가 아주 바빠서..
- No, Mom, I don't....
- I'm really busy--
잘들 다녀와요
So, you're going.
누구나 성장의 여지가
있다고 생각해요
And I think everyone
has room to grow...
그런데 그이는
자기만족에 빠져서
but Bob is perfectly satisfied...
저더러 자기 마누라가 된 걸로
행복한 줄 알라잖아요
and says just being his wife
should make me happy.
미지, 딱 거기까지
Midge, let me stop you right there.
이번이 첫번째 상담이지만
당신 얘기를 들어보니까
I know we've had only one session,
but from what I'm hearing...
당신 말이 절대적으로 옳고
everything you say is
completely right...
남편 말은 절대적으로 틀렸어요
and everything Bob says
is completely wrong.
나 이 치료가 좋아질려고 해요
I think I'm gonna like therapy.
이 치료도 당신이
좋아지려고 하네요
I think therapy's gonna like you.
재키, 여기서 뭐하는 거야?
너 레슬링 싫어하잖아
Jackie, what are you doing here?
You hate wrestling.
마이클이 좋아하니까
마이클이 좋아하는 건 나도 좋아
Michael likes it,
and anything that Michael likes, I like.
난 마이클을 좋아하니까
'Cause I like Michael.
내 여자친구 장하다
Yeah, that's my girl.
토할 것 같아!
Oh, barf.
다리 조심해라
Come on, watch your legs.
애들 데리고 레슬링 보러 가나?
Taking the gang to
the wrestling matches?
나는 저녁내내 집에
혼자 있을 것 같아
I guess I'll just sit
home alone tonight...
집사람이 심리치료를
받으러 간다나 뭐라나
since Midge is going
to some therapy thing.
나 혼자 외롭게
I'll be alone.
차에 타게, 밥
Get in the car, Bob.
- 에릭, 차 키 줘라
- 왜 제가 운전하면 안 돼요?
- Eric, give me the keys.
- Why can't I drive?
난 몸 성히 가고 싶으니까
Because I want to get
there in one piece.
좀 빨리 가면 안 돼요?
Hey, can we get a move on?
난쟁이 20명이 자유시합하는 거 놓치면
저 정말 왕 삐짐이에요
If I Miss that 20-midget free-for-all,
I'm gonna be super pissed.
좋아요. 직접 하세요
Fine. You drive.
여보
Red.
다시 생각해 보니까
네가 하는 게 낫겠다
You know, on second thought
you should drive.
오늘밤 나는 네 친구니까
After all, tonight I'm just
one of the gang.
이건 실수하는 거야, 알았어?
우린 서로 잡아먹으려고 들거라고
This isn't gonna work, you know?
We're gonna kill each other.
좋네요, 서로 잡아 먹어요
둘이서 같이만 하면 돼요
Fine, kill each other.
Just do it together.
핸들을 두손으로 잡아라, 에릭
Both hands on the wheel, Eric.
10시와 2시 위치에 손을 놔
10 and 2. 10 and 2
- 아빠, 직접 운전하고 싶으시면..
- 아니다. 괜찮다
- Dad, if you want to drive....
- No. That's all right.
난 그냥 네 친구중에 하나야
I'm just one of the gang.
양보, 젠장!
저 표지판에 "양보"라고 써 있잖아
Yield, damn it!
That sign says, "yield."
훨씬 낫군
That's better.
이게 뭔 짓거리야
This is ridiculous.
집에 가서는 네 엄마한테 재밌어서
죽을 뻔 했다고 말하는게 좋을거다
When we get home tonight...
you better tell your mother
we had a damn good time.
아직까지는 괜찮네요
So far so good.
그래
Yeah.
난 이제 10센트짜리 맥주
2달러에 사 마시러 가야 겠다
And now, I gotta go
and spend $2 for a 10-cent beer.
아빠들하고 같이 오게 돼서
좋아 죽겠어
Gee, I'm so glad our dads came.
그래도 너희 아빠는
멀찌감치 계시잖아 / 그래
At least yours is leaving
you alone. / Yeah.
- 가엾은 페즈, 그치?
- 맞아
- Poor Fez, huh?
- Yeah.
난 부엌에 앉아 있었어
There I was sitting in the kitchen.
부엌에 앉아있는데, 허걱!
도나엄마가 심리치료를 받겠다는 거야
Sitting in the kitchen, when, boom!
She tells me she needs therapy.
집사람이랑 나는
사이가 좋았단다, 페지
Yeah, Midge and I
had a beautiful thing, Fezzy...
근데 그게 다 어긋나 버렸어
then it all went wrong.
맞아요, 아저씨
여자들이 문제죠
Yeah, Bob, women are hell.
우리 다같이 맥주 한잔하면서
얘기해 보는게 어때요?
Why don't you grab us all a beer
and we'll talk it over?
너희들은 미성년자니까
소다는 사줄 수 있어
I could get you sodas,
'cause I know you're underage.
우리 얘기를 하는게 아니잖아요
Bob, this isn't about us.
아저씨 얘기라구요
It's about you.
게다가 말벗이 필요하시구요
And you need friends.
맥주도요
And beer.
날 바보라고 생각하는 거냐?
How stupid do you think I am?
맥주 한잔하면서
그것도 얘기해 보죠 뭐
Why don't we grab a beer
and we'll talk it over?
안돼
No.
그럼 혼자 잘해 보세요
Then, Bob, you're on your own.
이러니까 아저씨가 왕따 당하죠
See how you drive people away?
심리치료 한번 받고 나면
몸이 느슨해 지는 것 같다니까요
I'm telling you, after my therapy
session, I felt so loose.
느슨해지는 거 좋죠
loose: '헤프다'라는 의미도 있음
Loose is good.
내 생각에 우린 좀
타이트해져야 될 것 같은데요
If you ask me, we could all
do with a little tightening.
오늘밤에 내 심리치료사가
집단 심리치료를 한다는데
And tonight, my therapist is hosting
an encounter group...
혼자가기는 좀 쑥스러워서요
but I'm too shy to go alone.
저런, 안됐네요
- Well, too bad.
- Kitty, please come with me.
키티, 나랑 같이 가줘요
그러고 싶지 않네요
고맙지만 싫어요
I don't think so. No, thank you. No.
옛날에 기억 안나요?
You know what this is a lot like?
자기가 나한테 자선행사때 팔
빵 만드는 거 도와달라고 부탁한 거요
Like when you asked me
to help you host the bake sale.
그때 나는 "좋다"고 했었는데..
Only it's different,
because I said yes.
- 알았어요
- 고마워요
- All right.
- Great.
그 사람이 치료중인 영혼들이
모이는 거예요, 술 한잔 하면서요
It's a gathering of his souls
in progress. Over drinks.
술 공짜예요? 나도 갈래요
Free drinks? I'm in.
잘한다. 아주 이쁜 소리만
골라서 하는구나
That's nice.
That's music to a mother's ears.
어떻게 돼가냐?
Okay, what's going on here?
링위에 있는 저 사람 보이시죠?
저 사람이 로키 존슨인데
실제 로키 존슨의 아들인 레슬러 "더 락"
Okay, you see the guy getting
in the ring? That's Rocky Johnson.
정말 최고예요
Man, he's the best.
최고는 무슨?
The best?
정말 싸우는 것도 아니잖아
저거 전부 트릭이야
They're not even fighters.
I mean, it's all tricks.
내가 당장 저위에 올라가서...
I could get up there
right now and--
이런, 저 녀석 머리부터
처박아 버렸어
Goddamn, he dropped that guy
right on his head!
Yeah!
좋았어. 잡았다
이 녀석 아무데도 못 간다
That's right. I got him.
He ain't going anywhere.
원, 투, 쓰리
One, two, three.
The winner!
저리 꺼져!
내가 이겼다
Get off me! I'm the winner here.
Yeah!
Man!
- 열기가 장난아닌데
- 이를 어째
- Hot in here.
- You poor thing.
- 좀 나아, 자기?
- 응
- Is that better, sweetie?
- Yeah!
- 재키, 잠깐 얘기 좀 할래?
- 알았어
Jackie, can I talk to you
for a second? / Yeah, sure.
마이클, 괜찮..
Michael, is it okay--
재키, 너 켈소랑 대체
어떻게 돼가는 거야?
Jackie, what the hell is going on
between you and Kelso?
마이클 켈소와 나는 아름다운
사랑을 만들고 있어/ 우엑!
Look, Michael Kelso and I
have made beautiful love. / EW!
내 말은..
I mean....
아니, 우엑 맞아
No, EW!
왜 네가 몸종 노릇을
자처하는 건데?
Why are you being
such a doormat?
난 잘 보여야 된단 말야
Look, I have to be nice.
쟤가 싫증이라도 내면 어떡해?
What if he gets bored now?
싫증? 재키, 저 녀석은
또 하고 싶어 할 게 뻔해
Bored? Jackie, he's gonna
want to do it again.
그러니까 네 말은
내가 주도권을 쥐고 있다는 거구나
So what you're saying is,
I'm totally in charge.
내말은 남녀관계란..
I mean, a partnership--
아냐. 내가 쟬 소유한 거야
내가 주인님이라고
No. I own him! I am the man.
재키.. / 아냐, 아냐
고마워, 도나
- Jackie--
- No. Thank you, Donna.
안녕하세요
시원한 콜라 한잔 주세요
Good evening, sir.
I would like a refreshing cola, please.
맥주도 한잔 사 오너라, 아들아
And get me a beer, son.
네, 아빠, 알았어요
저희 아빠 맥주도 한잔요
Okay, Dad, sure.
And a beer for my dad.
저한테 맥주 안 주실거죠, 그렇죠?
You're not gonna
get me that beer, are you?
무슨 문제가 있느냐, 아들아?
What seems to be
the problem, son?
뭐하는 거야?
거기 널부러져 있음 안되지!
What're you doing?
Don't just sit there!
일어나, 이 미련곰탱아!
봐, 저 녀석이 널 비웃고 있잖아!
Get up, you big moose!
Look, he's laughing at you!
나도 알아
I give and I give and I give!
나도 안다고
나도 안다니까!
징징거리지 말고 얼른 올라가!
Boo-hoo. Get back in the ring!
Come on.
야, 이거 재밌는데
Hey, this is fun.
로키 존슨? 존슨씨
사인 좀 해주실래요?
Rocky Johnson. Mr. Johnson, sir,
can I get your autograph?
로키! 로키! 로키!
Rocky!
에릭, 들어가서 사인받아 오렴
Eric, go in there
and get your autograph.
안돼요, 아빠
"선수 전용"이라고 써있잖아요
No way, Dad.
The sign says, "wrestlers only."
그래서?
So?
법규잖아요
So, that's a rule.
제가 기억하기로는
어떤 성인께서 제게 말씀하시길
As I remember,
a great man once said to me:
"우리가 법규를 지키지 않으면
"If we were to break the rules...
세상은 나무에 올라가서 헛소리나
날리는 놈들로 가득 찰 거다"라고 하셨어요
"the world would just be filled
with tree-climbing crapflingers."
잘났다. 따라와
사인이 받고 싶긴 한 거냐?
Yeah. Follow me.
You want your autograph or not?
여기 있구나
There he is.
존슨씨, 그 난쟁이 녀석들을
한방에 보내버리시다니 대단하세요!
Mr. Johnson, you gave that team
of midgets an ass whupping, sir!
쬐그만 녀석이랑 붙게 되면
관중들이 전부 날 적대시한단다
You pile drive a little guy
and the whole crowd turns on you.
그 위에서 싸우다 보면, 대체 왜
야유를 당해야 되는지 억울하다니까
When you're standing there,
wondering what they're booing about...
무릎까지 물려가면서 말이다
내 무릎 좀 봐라
you get bit on the kneecaps.
Look at my knees.
난쟁이가 물었어
Midget bites.
내 아들한테 사인 좀
해 주실 수 없을까요?
I wonder if you'd mind
giving my son an autograph.
안돼요
사인은 안됩니다
No.
No autographs.
이보시오
Look, pal...
여기서 실제로 사람 죽여본 사람은
아마 나 뿐일 게요
I might be the only guy in here
who's actually killed a man.
꼬마한테 사인 해줘
하지만 더이상은 안돼
Give the kid an autograph.
And then, no more autographs.
아들을 레슬링 시합에 데려오시다니
정말 자상하시군요
That's really nice.
Bringing your kid to a wrestling match.
나도 아들이 하나 있는데
You know, I've got a son.
언젠가 그 아이는 스포츠 엔터테인먼트
계에서 가장 빛나는 인물이 될 겁니다
And one day, he's gonna become
the most electrifying man...
in sports entertainment.
네, 행운을 빌겠소
Yeah, good luck with that.
Wanna make that out to Red Forman?
사인은 '레드 포먼에게'로 해 주겠소?
아뇨, 그게 아니에요
에릭 포먼이에요, 대문자 E-R-I-C로요
No. I don't think so.
It's Eric Forman. Capital E-R-I-C.
- 맞소, 그런데 이녀석 별명이 레드라오
- 아뇨, 아니에요. 에릭이에요
- Yeah, but see, his nickname is Red.
- No, it's not, it's Eric.
농담 그만 해라, 레드!
Stop kidding around, Red!
자기, 이쯤해서 소다 한잔 마시면
끝내 줄 것 같은데 말야
You know, babe, a soda would
taste pretty good right about now.
맞아, 소다가 좋을 것 같다
Yeah, you're right.
A soda does sound pretty good.
- 난 다이어트로 할래
- 그래, 난 루트 비어
- I'll have a diet.
- Yeah, I'll have a root beer.
날 위해 다녀오고 싶지 않은 거야?
Don't you want to go get it for me?
자기?
Sweetie?
좋아, 널 위해서 확실히 해줄께
Okay, let me clear it up for you.
가서 소다 사와
Get me a soda.
당장!
Now!
봤니? 내가 주인이야
Did you see that?
I'm the man.
모든 건 6개월전에 시작됐단다
It all started about six months ago...
집사람이 코스모 잡지를
구독하면서 말야
when Midgie got
a subscription to Cosmo.
이 집단 심리치료는
These group sessions...
여러분의 한계를
시험해 보는 겁니다
are about testing your boundaries...
여러분의 억압된 감정을 표출해서
다른 사람과 공유하는 거죠
losing your inhibitions,
and really sharing with the group.
키티, 준비됐나요?
Kitty, are you ready?
조금만 해봐요, 엄마
Share a little, Mom.
행주를 똑바로 접으면
어떻게 만사가 해결되는지 말해줘요
Tell us how folding
the dishtowels just right...
makes all our problems go away.
내가 공유하길 원해요?
You want me to share?
알았어요
Okay.
로리, 넌 동생을 못 살게 굴고
대학에서는 막 나가고 있어
Laurie, you're mean to your brother
and you're screwing around at college.
빨아논 옷이나 돈이 떨어지기
전에는 콧배기도 안 비치지
We don't even see you
unless you run out of clean clothes...
or need cash.
사실 넌 배은망덕하고
버르장머리없는 년이야
The fact is,
you're an ungrateful, spoiled brat.
어머, 고마워요
이거 정말 괜찮네요
Well, thank you. That was nice.
사랑한다, 얘야
I love you, honey.
그럼, 이 여행에 대해 다들
저처럼 흥분되셨으면 좋겠네요
Well, I hope you're all as excited...
about this journey as I am.
둘씩 짝을 지읍시다
Let's pair off.
우리 가요
Okay, we're leaving.
난 잘 모르겠어요, 키티
어떻게 된 거예요?
I don't get it, Kitty.
What's going on?
어떻게 된건지 말해 줄게요
저 치는 사이비예요
I'll tell you what's going on.
He's a bad doctor.
아주 더러운 사이비요
A very bad doctor.
아빠, 돌아올 때
제가 운전하게 해 주셔서 고마워요
Dad, thanks for letting
me drive home.
안 죽고 오게 해줘서 고맙다
Thanks for not killing me.
있죠, 오늘 저녁
정말 즐거웠어요, 아빠
You know, I just had a lot of
fun tonight with you, Dad.
그래, 나도 마찬가지다
Yeah, me too.
좋아요, 해요
All right, let's go.
- 해 보겠다?
- 네
- Want some?
- Yeah.
어디 잡혀만 보세요
I wanna have a piece.
이제 누가 짱이죠?
누가 짱이냐구요?
Yes! Who's the king?
Who's the king?
- 아, 목이야!
- 이런, 아빠 죄송해요
- My neck!
- Gosh, Dad, I'm sorry.
정말 죄송해요
모르고 그런..
I'm so sorry.
Look, I had no--
이제 누가 짱이라고?
Now who's the king?
아빠요
You are.
그 심리치료사는 섹스에
환장한 놈이었던 거에요
And it turned out this therapist
was just obsessed with sex.
그래서 전 너무 힘들어요
And this is a really difficult time for me.
나는 나를 진지하게 받아들이지 않는
의사는 필요 없어요
The last thing I need is a doctor
who doesn't take me seriously.
나는 내가 뭐든 말할 수 있고
내 얘기를 경청해 줄 사람이 필요해요
I need to find someone I can talk to,
someone who will really listen.
그래서...
So. Wanna go to a party?
파티에 갈래요?
좋아요
Okay.
번역수정: 김찬미(husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24